Dick Clark Papers
Dick Clark Papers
- Interviews
  - Recordings
    - Fox, Michael J., 04-05-1984; clark_d_090; accompanying note; Audio cassette (Box 168)
      Recording content from a note is [Side 1: same closeness Alex and Michael; not politically minded; conservative groups want his support; Buckley like Alex; change in Alex character-more sensitive; Real close relationship on set; Meredith teases in a 'motherly' way; misses family in Canada; moved to LA because of professional opportunities; wanted to be writer, musician, artist; age a problem-looks too old or young; can't project future-takes each project as it comes; likes all kinds of music-used to play in a band. like guitar music; liked Beatles because of older siblings; likes 'Blackbird' by Beatles-likes reflective songs; 1st public appearance on T.V. show in Canada 279 CBC 1st part; admires Dustin Hoffman, Paul Newman. likes Hoffman because he's small but convincing actor. tries not to have idols because he'll never attain heights as big as those on pedestal; Art Carney/Mavreen Stapleton helped inspire him; good student till discovered outside thingsSide 2: dresses casual because that's 'him'; big hockey fan; on bloopers-fun at home, insane feeling to participate; slipped during one episode-most embarrassing moment]
    - Franco, Ramon, 03-06-1989; clark_d_092; Audio cassette (Box 168)
    - Freeman, Morgan, 12-08-1989; clark_d_093; Audio cassette (Box 168)
    - Freleng, Friz, 05-16-1990; clark_d_095; Audio cassette (Box 168)
    - Frewer, Matt; Honey, I Shrunk the Kids, 05-30-1989; clark_d_096; Audio cassette (Box 168)
    - Friedman, Budd, 03-07-1989; clark_d_094; Audio cassette (Box 168)
    - Fuller, Kurt [misspelled on label as Curt], 05-18-1990; clark_d_097; Audio cassette (Box 168)
    - Furst, Stephen, 05-01-1989; clark_d_098; Audio cassette (Box 168)
    - Gallagher, Megan, 08-03-1989; clark_d_099; Audio cassette (Box 168)
    - George, Phyllis, 11-27-1989; clark_d_100; Audio cassette (Box 168)
    - Gian, Joseph [misspelled on label as Joesph], 05-04-1990; clark_d_101; Audio cassette (Box 168)
    - Gibbons, Leeza, 06-29-1989; clark_d_102; Audio cassette (Box 168)
    - Gibson, Mel, [undated]; clark_d_103; Audio cassette (Box 168)
    - Glen, Iain, [undated]; clark_d_104; Audio cassette (Box 168)
    - Goldberg, George, 03-03-1989; clark_d_105; Audio cassette (Box 168)
    - Goldin, Ricky Paull, 03-16-1990; clark_d_106; Audio cassette (Box 168)
    - Gould, Harold, 06-05-1990; clark_d_107; Audio cassette (Box 168)
    - Greene, Lorne, 01-16-1985; clark_d_108; Audio cassette (Box 168)
    - Grelun, Landon, See Presley, Elvis.
    - Groener, Harry, 03-12-1990; clark_d_109; Audio cassette (Box 168)
    - Grossman, Sam, 04-14-1989; clark_d_110; Audio cassette (Box 168)
    - Guillaume, Robert [misspelled on label as Guillame], 07-26-1989; clark_d_111; Audio cassette (Box 168)
    - Hanks, Tom, 05-31-1984; clark_d_112; accompanying note; Audio cassette (Box 168)
      Summary of recording content, from notes: Bosom Buddies-got part after auditioning from ABC and doing tests; B.B written by good writers; wasn't surprised by its success; took awhile to adjust to women's costumes; series on for two years because everyone had a good time; learned to juggle because Peter Scolari a good juggler; didn't know 'Splash' was gonna take off that well. knew good people working on it; Ron Howard a taskmaster and pushed him to be a good actor. They developed a good communication and would accept nothing but the best from him; Didn't have one bad criticism of 'Splash.' Every frame counted. Old fashioned story/character movie; didn't want to be an actor until later. Wanted to be involved in theatre. Worked in Shakespeare festival and surrounded by professionals. And after doing that for 6 years realized acting was a good living; First job was big break-breaks come in continuing stream. B.B. brought exposure 'Splash' helped because big budget picture. First job giving him union card was first big break; never played musical instrument really except for violin for 6 months; has to learn violin for movie; 'Bachelor Party' came up suddenly. Just wrapped 'Splash' and was exhausted but made decision quickly. Great role of iconoclast; personal life hasn't changed too much. T.V. show gave him first taste of celebrity; sometimes it does cause a panic like when he was in an airport and busload of teens almost jumped him; doesn't bother him when people ask him about B.B.-flattered because of cult following; The scripts come in continuously but some or none will end up made; Shoots for variety in movies-Bachelor Party different from Splash. Variety in roles keeps him going. isn't typecast; has respect for stand-up comedians. used to think life of an actor was itinerant, but nothing compared to that of stand p comic. Stand up routine like writing a novel; Doesn't see any order to his career. Most important thing is to have variety in roles. Lot of good roles in mediocre movies and bad roles in great movies-hard to decide; Advice-be willing to move around. don't get too secure.
    - Hanks, Tom, 02-22-1990; clark_d_113; Audio cassette (Box 168)
    - Harper, Valerie, 03-07-1990; clark_d_114; Audio cassette (Box 168)
    - Harris, Mel, 01-18-1990; clark_d_115; Audio cassette (Box 168)
    - Hauer, Rutger, 01-25-1990; clark_d_116; Audio cassette (Box 168)
    - Hays, Robert, 02-01-1990; clark_d_117; Audio cassette (Box 169)
    - Hefner, Hugh, 05-01-1984; clark_d_118; Audio cassette (Box 169)
    - Helgenberg, Marg, 01-15-1990; clark_d_119; Audio cassette (Box 169)
    - Helmond, Katherine, Mar 23 [no year]; clark_d_120; Audio cassette (Box 169)
    - Heston, Charlton, 05-16-1990; clark_d_121; Audio cassette (Box 169)
    - Hewett, Christopher, 01-17-1990; clark_d_122; Audio cassette (Box 169)
    - Hillerman, John, Mar 29 [no year]; clark_d_123; Audio cassette (Box 169)
    - Hirsch, David, 07-19-1989; clark_d_124; Audio cassette (Box 169)
    - Hofmann, Isabella [misspelled on label as Hoffmann], 03-12-1990; clark_d_125; Audio cassette (Box 169)
    - Holliday, Fred, 11-16-1989; clark_d_126; Audio cassette (Box 169)
    - Hope, Bob, 05-16-1984; clark_d_127; Audio cassette (Box 169)
    - Howard, Arliss, 01-29-1990; clark_d_128; Audio cassette (Box 169)
    - Howard, Jean, [undated]; clark_d_129; Audio cassette (Box 169)
    - Howe, Bones, 12-06-1984; clark_d_130; Audio cassette (Box 169)
    - Hudson, Ernie, 05-30-1989; clark_d_131; Audio cassette (Box 169)
    - Hufsey, Billy, 1984; clark_d_132; Audio cassette (Box 169)
    - Hurt, John on "Scandal", Apr 1989; clark_d_133; Audio cassette (Box 169)
    - Iovine, Jimmy, 05-25-1984; clark_d_134; Audio cassette (Box 169)
    - James, Billy, 04-26-1984; clark_d_135; Audio cassette (Box 169)
    - Jewell, Geri, 03-27-1990; clark_d_136; Audio cassette (Box 169)
    - Jillian, Ann, 02-15-1990; clark_d_137; Audio cassette (Box 169)
    - Jones, Jack, Apr 12 [no year]; clark_d_140; Audio cassette (Box 169)
    - Jones, James Earl, 05-16-1990; clark_d_138; Audio cassette (Box 169)
    - Jones, John Bev., 04-26-1984; clark_d_139; Audio cassette (Box 169)
    - Joyce, Elaine [misspelled on label as Elayne], 07-26-1989; clark_d_141; Audio cassette (Box 169)
    - Kaake, Jeff, 04-13-1990; clark_d_142; Audio cassette (Box 169)
    - Kanan, Sean, 06-01-1989; clark_d_143; Audio cassette (Bo 169)
    - Kane, Carol, 01-30-1990; clark_d_144; Audio cassette (Box 169)
    - Karman, Janice, See Bagdasarian, Ross; Karman, Janice; The Chipmunks.
    - Kassir, John, 04-17-1990; clark_d_145; Audio cassette (Box 169)
    - Katzman, Leonard, 05-12-1984; clark_d_146; Audio cassette (Box 169)
    - Keanan, Staci; "My Two Dads", [undated]; clark_d_147; Audio cassette (Box 169)
    - Keach, James [misspelled on label as Keech], 04-26-1989; clark_d_148; Audio cassette (Box 169)
    - King, Zalman [misspelled on label as Zelman], 04-05-1990; clark_d_150; Audio cassette (Box 150)
    - Kiser, Terry: Weekend at Bernie's [misspelled on label as Teri Keiser], 05-18-1989; clark_d_149; Audio cassette (Box 169)
    - Kober, Jeff, 09-22-1989; clark_d_151; Audio cassette (Box 169)
    - Kopelson, Arnold, 12-05-1989; clark_d_152; Audio cassette (Box 169)
    - Kreppel, Paul, 02-24-1989; clark_d_153; Audio cassette (Box 169)
    - Ladd, Diane, [undated]; clark_d_154; Audio cassette (Box 169)
    - Lambert, Christopher, 02-07-1990; clark_d_155; Audio cassette (Box 169)
    - Landers, Audrey, May 12 [no year]; clark_d_156; Audio cassette (Box 169)
    - Landers, Audrey; Landers, Judy, 06-01-1990; clark_d_160; Audio cassette (Box 169)
    - Lane, Diane, 03-23-1990; clark_d_157; Audio cassette (Box 169)
    - Lasorda, Tommy, 04-19-1984; clark_d_158; Audio cassette (Box 169)
    - Laurie, Piper, 03-28-1990; clark_d_159; Audio cassette (Box 169)
    - Lawrence, Matthew, 08-04-1989; clark_d_161; Audio cassette (Box 169)
    - Lawrence, Vicki, [undated]; clark_d_162; Audio cassette (Box 169)
    - Lee, Michele, 05-02-1990; clark_d_163; Audio cassette (Box 169)
    - Leisure, David, 08-09-1989; clark_d_164; Audio cassette (Box 169)
    - Levine, Steve, 06-22-1984; clark_d_165; Audio cassette (Box 169)
    - Linke, Paul, 07-10-1989; clark_d_166; Audio cassette (Box 169)
    - Lowe, Rob, [undated]; clark_d_167; Audio cassette (Box 169)
    - Lynn, Diana, 04-13-1984; clark_d_168; Audio cassette (Box 169)
    - Magnuson, Ann, 03-08-1990; clark_d_169; Audio cassette (Box 169)
    - Maltin, Leonard, 03-14-1989; clark_d_170; Audio cassette (Box 169)
    - Mancini, Henry, 11-27-1989; clark_d_171; Audio cassette (Box 169)
    - Martin, Andrea, 06-26-1989; clark_d_172; Audio cassette (Box 169)
    - Martin, Jared, 04-06-1989; clark_d_173; Audio cassette (Box 169)
    - Martin, Kellie [misspelled on label as Kelly], 05-09-1990; clark_d_174; Audio cassette (Box 170)
    - Matthau, Charles [misspelled on label as Mathau], 05-04-1989; clark_d_175; Audio cassette (Box 170)
    - Matthau, Walter [misspelled on label as Mathau], 01-15-1989; clark_d_176; Audio cassette (Box 170)
    - McClurg, Edie [misspelled on label as McClourg], 04-25-1989; clark_d_177; Audio cassette (Box 170)
    - McClure, Paula: "Inside Video", 09-20-1989; clark_d_178; Audio cassette (Box 170)
    - McCord, Kent, [undated]; clark_d_181; Audio cassette (Box 170)
    - McDonald, Christopher, 02-09-1990; clark_d_179; Audio cassette (Box 170)
    - McKean, Michael, 01-31-1990; clark_d_180; Audio cassette (Box 170)
    - Medley, Odis, 07-30-1984; clark_d_182; Audio cassette (Box 170)
    - Meriwether, Lee [misspelled on label as Merriwether], 05-21-1990; clark_d_183; Audio cassette (Box 170)
    - Messick, Don, 06-21-1990; clark_d_184; Audio cassette (Box 170)
    - Mills, Donna, 03-24-1984; clark_d_185; accompanying note; Audio cassette (Box 170)
      Summary of contents, based on notes found with recording: Abby Ewing; Knot's Landing; exercises anytime; schedule; dancing
    - Mills, Hayley [misspelled on label as Haley], 01-31-1990; clark_d_186; Audio cassette (Box 170)
    - Miziker, [Ron], See Despie, [Dennis] and Miziker, [Ron].
    - Moroder, Giorgio, 08-13-1984; clark_d_187; Audio cassette (Box 170)
    - Morton, Joe, 02-07-1990; clark_d_188; Audio cassette (Box 170)
    - Mulgrew, Kate, 04-10-1989; clark_d_189; Audio cassette (Box 170)
    - Murphy, Terry [misspelled on label as Murphey], 01-11-1990; clark_d_190; Audio cassette (Box 170)
    - Nelson, Sandy, 1985; clark_d_191; Audio cassette (Box 170)
    - Neufeld, Mace; Connery Sean #1, [undated]; clark_d_192; Audio cassette (Box 170)
    - Nevius, Craig, 03-04-1990; clark_d_193; Audio cassette (Box 170)
    - Noone, Peter, Apr 22 [no year]; clark_d_194; Audio cassette (Box 170)
    - O'Neill, Ed [misspelled on label as O'Neil], 05-02-1989; clark_d_197; Audio cassette (Box 170)
    - Olmos, Edward James, 12-06-1989; clark_d_195; Audio cassette (Box 170)
    - Omartian, Michael, 10-04-1984; clark_d_196; Audio cassette (Box 170)
    - Overall, Park, 02-09-1990; clark_d_198; Audio cassette (Box 170)
    - Parker, Sarah Jessica, 03-07-1990; clark_d_199; Audio cassette (Box 170)
    - Pax, James, 04-09-1990; clark_d_200; Audio cassette (Box 170)
    - Peck, Cecilia, 05-29-1990; clark_d_201; Audio cassette (Box 170)
    - Perry, Felton; Hooperman, 03-06-1989; clark_d_202; Audio cassette (Box 170)
    - Perry, Matthew, 04-03-1990; clark_d_203; Audio cassette (Box 170)
    - Phillips, Lou Diamond, 03-29-1990; clark_d_205; Audio cassette (Box 170)
    - Picardo, Robert, 12-21-1989; clark_d_204; Audio cassette (Box 170)
    - Presley, Elvis; Landon Grelun, [undated]; clark_d_206; Audio cassette (Box 170)
      Summary of contents, based on label: Eddie Rabbitt; E. Rabbitt; Steve Allen; Bobby Vinton; Chaka Kahn; Robert 'Kool' Bell
    - Saget, Bob; Full House, 06-21-1989; clark_d_207; Audio cassette (Box 170)
    - St. Gerard, Michael, 03-11-1990; clark_d_223; Audio cassette (Box 170)
    - Sajak, Pat, 04-19-1984; clark_d_208; Audio cassette (Box 170)
      Summary of contents, based on note included with recording: college bowl anniversary; worried he'd look like a 'moron'; can't plan linearly; used to working live; people mis-guess puzzles on wheel; move from Nashville to L.A. no problem; doesn't miss doing weather; Jack Paar his idol; used to talk into spoons; always wanted to 'broadcast'; content being himself; happy being a broadcaster; glad to be doing what he's doing; no hobbies but broadcasting
    - Sanderson, Bill, 02-05-1990; clark_d_209; Audio cassette (Box 170)
    - Schuck, John, 05-21-1990; clark_d_210; Audio cassette (Box 170)
    - Shales, Tom, 12-19-1989; clark_d_211; Audio cassette (Box 170)
    - Shapiro, Arnold, 02-22-1990; clark_d_212; Audio cassette (Box 170)
    - Shatner, William, [undated]; clark_d_213; Audio cassette (Box 170)
    - Shields, Brooke, 03-31-1984; clark_d_214; Audio cassette (Box 170)
      Summary of contents, based on note included with recording: debut at 9 with modeling; acting logical progression; working; learning process 'I feel like...this big meal'; wants to play older character; strong type; wants to dance; takes aerobics and make films; in Princeton triangle; lee's exercise; balance of school and work; shopping and eating caught up in studies; albums she likes; likes all kinds of music; advice to young actors "many people...in making a film when I think of it glamour part
    - Shore, Pauly, 07-31-1989; clark_d_215; Audio cassette (Box 170)
    - Shriner, Wil, 05-01-1989; clark_d_216; Audio cassette (Box 170)
    - Sikking, James, [undated]; clark_d_217; Audio cassette (Box 170)
    - Silverman, Stephen, 11-30-1989; clark_d_218; Audio cassette (Box 170)
    - Sirtis, Marina, 04-06-1990; clark_d_219; Audio cassette (Box 170)
    - Smith, Lane, 06-08-1990; clark_d_220; Audio cassette (Box 170)
    - Smits, Jimmy, 03-29-1990; clark_d_221; Audio cassette (Box 170)
    - Soul, David, [undated]; clark_d_222; Audio cassette (Box 170)
    - Steinfeld, Jake, 11-30-1989; clark_d_224; Audio cassette (Box 170)
    - Stevens, Stella, Mar 28 [no year]; clark_d_225; Audio cassette (Box 170)
    - Stewart, James, 03-05-1990; clark_d_226; Audio cassette (Box 170)
    - Stewart, Patrick, [undated]; clark_d_227; Audio cassette (Box 170)
    - Stone, Chris, Mar 1984; clark_d_228; Audio cassette (Box 170)
    - Suchet, David, 01-05-1990; clark_d_229; Audio cassette (Box 170)
    - Summer, Cree, 02-24-1986; clark_d_230; Audio cassette (Box 170)
    - Szarabajka, Keith, 07-27-1989; clark_d_231; Audio cassette (Box 171)
    - Taxier, Arthur, [undated]; clark_d_232; Audio cassette (Box 171)
    - Taylor, Meshach, 06-23-1989; clark_d_233; Audio cassette (Box 171)
    - Thaw, John, 01-05-1990; clark_d_234; Audio cassette (Box 171)
    - Thomas, Dave, 01-17-1990; clark_d_235; Audio cassette (Box 171)
    - Thomas, Richard, 01-04-1990; clark_d_236; Audio cassette (Box 171)
    - [Untitled], [undated]; clark_d_237; Audio cassette (Box 171)
- Proposals
  - Decisions -- Decisions!, audience participation game (Box 5)
  - The Hunted, premise and outline for pilot episode (Box 5)
  - The Many Worlds of Christopher Wells, script for proposed[?] episode (Box 5)
  - Melrose Beanstock...Mayor, half-hour sitcom (Box 5)
  - The Record Years, taped tv special (Box 5)
  - Under Cloud Nine, screen musical; multiple copies of long and short versions; 3 folders (Box 6)
  - Where It's At, weekly variety show (Box 6)
  - The Winner's Circle, weekly music show (Box 6)
- Recordings, Countdown America (CDA)
  The majority of these are 14" reels with a few 9" reels. In some cases there are multiple copies (either complete or partial), so an individual show may encompass anywhere from 1 to 19 reels. Voice tracks are not separate. Featured artists include Kenny Loggins, Paul Simon, the Commodores, Diana Ross, Sheena Easton, Bob Seger, Huey Lewis & the News, and many more.
  - Show #001, 4 tapes (Oversize 1)
  - Show #002, 8 tapes (Oversize 1)
  - Show #003, 8 tapes (Oversize 1-2)
  - Show #004, 8 tapes (Oversize 2-3)
  - Show #005, 8 tapes (Oversize 3)
  - Show #006, 8 tapes (Oversize 3-4)
  - Show #007, 8 tapes (Oversize 4)
  - Show #008, 6 tapes; lacking 4A, 1B (Oversize 5)
  - Show #009, 8 tapes (Oversize 5)
  - Show #010, Jan 1, 1986; 8 tapes (Oversize 6)
  - Show #011, Jan 11-12, 1986; 8 tapes (Oversize 6-7)
  - Show #012, Jan 18-19, 1986; 8 tapes (Oversize 7)
  - Show #013, Jan 25-26, 1986; 8 tapes (Oversize 7-8)
  - Show #014, Feb 1-2, 1986; 8 tapes (Oversize 8-9)
  - Show #015, Feb 8-9, 1986; 8 tapes (Oversize 9)
  - Show #016, Feb 15-16, 1986; 8 tapes (Oversize 9-10)
  - Show #017, Feb 22-23, 1986; 8 tapes (Oversize 10)
  - Show #018, Mar 1-2, 1986; 8 tapes (Oversize 11)
  - Show #019, Mar 8-9, 1986; 8 tapes (Oversize 11-12)
  - Show #020, Mar 15-16, 1986; 8 tapes (Oversize 12)
  - Show #021, Mar 22-23, 1986; 8 tapes (Oversize 12-13)
  - Show #022, Mar 29-30, 1986; 8 tapes (Oversize 13-14)
  - Show #023, Apr 5-6, 1986; 8 tapes (Oversize 14)
  - Show #024, Apr 12-13, 1986; 8 tapes (Oversize 14-15)
  - Show #025, Apr 19-20, 1986; 8 tapes (Oversize 15)
  - Show #026, Apr 26-27, 1986; 8 tapes (Oversize 15-16)
  - Show #027, May 3-4, 1986; 8 tapes (Oversize 16-17)
  - Show #028, May 10-11, 1986; 8 tapes (Oversize 17)
  - Show #029, May 17-18, 1986; 8 tapes (Oversize 17-18)
  - Show #030, May 24-25, 1986; 8 tapes (Oversize 18)
  - Show #031, May 31-Jun 1, 1986; 8 tapes (Oversize 19)
  - Show #032, Jun 7-8, 1986; 8 tapes (Oversize 19-20)
  - Show #033, Jun 14-15, 1986; 8 tapes (Oversize 20)
  - Show #034, Jun 21-22, 1986; 8 tapes (Oversize 20-21)
  - Show #035, Jun 28-29, 1986; 8 tapes (Oversize 21-22)
  - Show #036, Jul 5-6, 1986; 8 tapes (Oversize 22)
  - Show #037, Jul 12-13, 1986; 8 tapes (Oversize 22-23)
  - Show #038, Jul 19-20, 1986; 8 tapes (Oversize 23)
  - Show #039, Jul 26-27, 1986; 8 tapes (Oversize 23-24)
  - Show #040, Aug 2-3, 1986; 8 tapes (Oversize 24-25)
  - Show #041, Aug 9-10, 1986; 8 tapes (Oversize 25)
  - Show #042, Aug 16-17, 1986; 8 tapes (Oversize 25-26)
  - Show #043, Aug 23-24, 1986; 8 tapes (Oversize 26)
  - Show #044, Aug 30-31, 1986; 8 tapes (Oversize 26-27)
  - Show #045, Sep 6-7, 1986; 8 tapes (Oversize 27-28)
  - Show #046, Sep 13-14, 1986; 8 tapes (Oversize 28)
  - Show #047, Sep 20-21, 1986; 8 tapes (Oversize 28-29)
  - Show #048, Sep 27-28, 1986; 8 tapes (Oversize 29)
  - Show #049, Oct 4-5, 1986; 7 tapes; lacking 1A (Oversize 30)
  - Show #050, Oct 11-12, 1986; 8 tapes (Oversize 30-31)
  - Show #051, Oct 18-19, 1986; 8 tapes (Oversize 31)
  - Show #052, Oct 25-26, 1986; 8 tapes (Oversize 31-32)
  - Show #053, Nov 1-2, 1986; 8 tapes (Oversize 32)
  - Show #054, Nov 8-9, 1986; 8 tapes (Oversize 33)
  - Show #055, Nov 15-16, 1986; 3 tapes; lacking 2A, 3A, 2B, 3B, 4B (Oversize 33)
  - Show #056, Nov 22-23, 1986; 8 tapes (Oversize 33-34)
  - Show #057, Nov 29-30, 1986; 8 tapes (Oversize 34-35)
  - Show #058, Dec 6-7, 1986; 8 tapes (Oversize 35)
  - Show #059, Dec 13-14, 1986; 8 tapes (Oversize 35-36)
  - Show #060, Dec 20-21, 1986; 8 tapes (Oversize 36)
  - Show #061, Dec 27-28, 1986; 7 tapes; lacking 3B (Oversize 36-37)
  - Show #062, Jan 3-4, 1987; 8 tapes (Oversize 37-38)
  - Show #063, Jan 10-11, 1987; 8 tapes (Oversize 38)
  - Show #064, Jan 17-18, 1987; 8 tapes (Oversize 38-39)
  - Show #065, Jan 24-25, 1987; 8 tapes (Oversize 39)
  - Show #066, Jan 31-Feb 1, 1987; 8 tapes (Oversize 39-40)
  - Show #067, Feb 7-8, 1987; 8 tapes (Oversize 40-41)
  - Show #068, Feb 14-15, 1987; 8 tapes (Oversize 41)
  - Show #069, Feb 21-22, 1987; 8 tapes (Oversize 41-42)
  - Show #070, Feb 28-Mar 1, 1987; 8 tapes (Oversize 42)
  - Show #071, Mar 7-8, 1987; 8 tapes (Oversize 43)
  - Show #072, Mar 14-15, 1987; 8 tapes (Oversize 43-44)
  - Show #073, Mar 21-22, 1987; 8 tapes (Oversize 44)
  - Show #074, Mar 28-29, 1987; 8 tapes (Oversize 44-45)
  - Show #075, Apr 4-5, 1987; 8 tapes (Oversize 45-46)
  - Show #076, Apr 11-12, 1987; 8 tapes (Oversize 46)
  - Show #077, Apr 18-19, 1987; 8 tapes (Oversize 46-47)
  - Show #078, Apr 25-26, 1987; 8 tapes (Oversize 47)
  - Show #079, May 2-3, 1987; 8 tapes (Oversize 47-48)
  - Show #080, May 9-10, 1987; 8 tapes (Oversize 48-49)
  - Show #081, May 16-17, 1987; 8 tapes (Oversize 49)
  - Show #082, May 23-24, 1987; 9 tapes; extra 3B (Oversize 49-50)
    Year/source: 1986 (LP
    Artist: Thompson Twins
  - Show #083, May 30-31, 1987; 8 tapes (Oversize 50-51)
    Year/source: 1985 (LP
    Artist: Kenny Loggins
  - Show #084, Jun 6-7, 1987; 8 tapes (Oversize 51)
    Year/source: 1984 (LP
    Artist: Howard Jones
  - Show #085, Jun 13-14, 1987; 8 tapes (Oversize 51-52)
    Year/source: 1983 (LP
    Artist: Carly Simon
  - Show #086, Jun 20-21, 1987; 8 tapes (Oversize 52)
    Year/source: 1982 (LP
    Artist: Miami Sound Machine
  - Show #087, Jun 27-28, 1987; 8 tapes (Oversize 52-53)
    Year/source: 1981 (LP
    Artist: Paul Simon
  - Show #088, Jul 4-5, 1987; 8 tapes (Oversize 53-54)
    Year/source: 1980 (LP
    Artist: Commodores
  - Show #089, Jul 11-12, 1987; 8 tapes (Oversize 54)
    Artist: Joe Cocker
  - Show #090, Jul 18-19, 1987; 8 tapes (Oversize 54-55)
    Artist: Steve Winwood
  - Show #091, Jul 25-26, 1987; 8 tapes (Oversize 55)
    Artist: Diana Ross
  - Show #092, Aug 1-2, 1987; 8 tapes (Oversize 56)
    Artist: Laura Branigan
  - Show #093, Aug 8-9, 1987; 8 tapes (Oversize 56-57)
    Artist: Toto
  - Show #094, Aug 15-16, 1987; 8 tapes (Oversize 57)
    Artist: Jeffrey Osborne
  - Show #095, Aug 22-23, 1987; 8 tapes (Oversize 57-58)
    Year/source: 1980 (M)
    Artist: Sheena Easton
  - Show #096, Aug 29-30, 1987; 8 tapes (Oversize 58)
    Year/source: 1986 (M)
    Artist: Dan Fogelberg
  - Show #097, Sep 5-6, 1987; 8 tapes (Oversize 59)
    Artist: Anita Baker
  - Show #098, Sep 12-13, 1987; 8 tapes (Oversize 59-60)
    Year/source: 1984 (M)
    Artist: unknown
  - Show #099, Sep 19-20, 1987; 8 tapes (Oversize 60)
    Artist: Bob Seger
  - Show #100, Sep 26-27, 1987; 8 tapes (Oversize 60-61)
    Artist: Elton John
  - Show #101, Oct 3-4, 1987; 8 tapes (Oversize 61-62)
    Year/source: 1981 (M)
    Artist: Fleetwood Mac
  - Show #102, Oct 10-11, 1987; 8 tapes (Oversize 62)
    Artist: Donna Summer
  - Show #103, Oct 17-18, 1987; 8 tapes (Oversize 62-63)
    Artist: Doobie Brothers
  - Show #104, Oct 24-25, 1987; 8 tapes (Oversize 63)
    Artist: Bee Gees
  - Show #105, Oct 31-Nov 1, 1987; 8 tapes (Oversize 63-64)
    Artist: Whitney Houston
  - Show #106, Nov 7-8, 1987; 8 tapes (Oversize 64-65)
    Year/source: 1983, 1984 (LP
    Artist: Huey Lewis & the News
  - Show #107, Nov 14-15, 1987; 8 tapes (Oversize 65)
    Artist: Carpenters
  - Show #108, Nov 21-22, 1987; 8 tapes (Oversize 65-66)
    Artist: REO Speedwagon
  - Show #109, Nov 28-29, 1987; 8 tapes (Oversize 66)
    Artist: Kool & the Gang
  - Show #110, Dec 5-6, 1987; 8 tapes (Oversize 67)
    Artist: George Harrison